const data = [
  {
    category: "HTML",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Qual a regra que muda a cor do texto?",
        options: ["color", "background-color", "font-size", "transition"],
        answer: "color"
      },
      {
        question: "Pergunta 2?",
        options: ["opção 1", "opção 2", "opção 3", "opção 4"],
        answer: "opção 3"
      },
      {
        question: "PERGUNTA 3?",
        options: ["item 1", "item 2", "item 3", "item 4"],
        answer: "item 2"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    category: "CSS",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Qual a regra que muda a cor do texto?",
        options: ["color", "background-color", "font-size", "transition"],
        answer: "color"
      },
      {
        question: "Pergunta 2?",
        options: ["opção 1", "opção 2", "opção 3", "opção 4"],
        answer: "opção 3"
      },
      {
        question: "Pergunta 2?",
        options: ["opção 1", "opção 2", "opção 3", "opção 4"],
        answer: "opção 3"
      },
      {
        question: "Pergunta 2?",
        options: ["opção 1", "opção 2", "opção 3", "opção 4"],
        answer: "opção 3"
      },
      {
        question: "PERGUNTA 3?",
        options: ["item 1", "item 2", "item 3", "item 4"],
        answer: "item 2"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    category: "JAVASCRIPT",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Qual a regra que muda a cor do texto?",
        options: ["color", "background-color", "font-size", "transition"],
        answer: "color"
      },
      {
        question: "Pergunta 2?",
        options: ["opção 1", "opção 2", "opção 3", "opção 4"],
        answer: "opção 3"
      },
      {
        question: "Pergunta 2?",
        options: ["opção 1", "opção 2", "opção 3", "opção 4"],
        answer: "opção 3"
      },
      {
        question: "PERGUNTA 3?",
        options: ["item 1", "item 2", "item 3", "item 4"],
        answer: "item 2"
      }
    ]
  }
];

export default data;
